A Guide to the William Leete Stone Sr. and Jr. Collection
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #7215-a
William Leete Stone Sr. and Jr. Collection 1824-1894
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
7215-a
9 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Deposit [ 1963 Dec 17 ] 1967 Feb 20
Item Listing
- Manuscripts
  - Page 65 from History of the Buccaneers of America, n. d.; AMs, 1 p.
    [Includes ANS by William Leete Stone, Jr. on verso.]
  - List of works by William Leete Stone, Sr., n. d.; AMs, 1 p.
- Letters
  - William Leete Stone Sr. to [George Lathrop] Perkins, 1831 Aug 21; ALS, 3 p.
    [Discusses Iroquois Indians, whose history interested Stone; speculates on the spelling of the Chieftain's name, On-kos or Uncas; says that, after meeting the English colonists, the chief was sometimes called Paquim or Paquiam, as well as Unca; tries to get Perkins' help, as Perkins seems to be an authority on the subject.]
  - William Leete Stone, Jr. to Benson John Lossing, 1877 Jan 16; ALS, 1 p.
    [Asks him to become one of his subscribers; says he is convinced that he will enjoy the publication.]
  - William Leete Stone, Jr. to Benson John Lossing, 1877 Dec 4; Printed Postcard
    [In Stone's hand; asks him to remit $2.25, the price of
    Bargain
    . ]
  - William Leete Stone, Jr. to Benson John Lossing, 1877 Dec 31; ALS, 2 p.
    [Discusses the publication of
    and related financial matters.]
  - William Leete Stone, Jr. to Joseph [Bradford] Carr, 1885 Nov 23; ALS, 2 p.
    [Requests volume XV of the
    Colonial History of New York
  - William Leete Stone, Jr. to H. Norris, Jr., 1894 Mar 10; ALS, 1 p.
    [Sends him the first installment [of autographs] on loan.]
  - William Leete Stone, Jr. to H. Norris, Jr., 1894 Mar 12; ALS, 2 p.
    [Says he has sent off more autograph letters to Norris with the promise of more to come; thanks him for the subscription; advises him on the arrangement of his autograph collection.]